[Music]
hello friends
welcome to icsi direct research videos
this is devon but from icsi direct
research team
and today i am going to discuss q1 fi 22
results of infosys infosys reported
robust revenue growth and was above our
estimate
in terms of peer comparison tcs has
underperformed infosys
and infosys is expected to do well going
forward as well
in terms of digital revenues the
company's revenue has grown
approximately 10
qrq and now contributes 54 percent of
the revenues and is expected to be key
crow driver going forward
in terms of deal pipeline the deal
pipeline has increased 24 percent qoq to
2.6 billion dollars
strong deal pipeline and revenue growth
has prompted
infosys to revise the revenue guidance
upwards from 12 to 14
to 14 to 16 percent in fy 22.
going forward we expect that vendor
consideration opportunities cost
takeouts
digital technologies a healthy deal
pipeline
will drive revenue growth for the
company the company has also increased
pressure highers from 25 000 to 35 000
to address attrition and demand
improved tech spend improving spend
across verticals and traction in cloud
supply chain customer experience cyber
securities
prompt us to believe that demand outlook
will remain robust in the medium term
further companies digital progress and
market share gains are expected to drive
revenues in the long run
all these efforts of the company will
lead to sustainable revenue growth in
the long run
the company aims to achieve 22 to 24
ebit margin
this will lead to sustainable revenue
and profitable growth this makes infosys
an
attractive play in the tech space
[Music]
you